

# Payam Zahedi MOBILE DEVELOPER

Experienced Mobile Developer with a solid 7+ years of experience in test-driven mobile app development, specializing in Flutter, Dart, and Android. Actively contributed to more than 10 projects, including being the maintainer of the Toastification, dart-persian-tools, and Fantom packages. Also made significant contributions to the development of the Fl-chart and flutter-spinkit packages. Co-founder of the Persian Flutter Community, organizing events, creating engaging content, and offering exciting challenges for Flutter developers. Strong teamwork and exceptional communication skills, consistently delivering high-quality work under tight deadlines. Committed to continuous learning and staying up-to-date with the latest trends and technologies in mobile app development.

💟 pzahedi1995@gmail.com 📞 +98- 939 - 066 - 2636 🔘 Iran

payam-zahedi

in payamzahedi95

### **EDUCATIONAL**

 Master of Software engineering Gorgan Azad University | 2017 - 2019 Bachelor of Software engineering Gorgan Azad University | 2013 - 2017

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

• Sep 2022 - Present Senior Mobile Developer, Snapp Mobile, Germany Remote • Jul 2021 - Sep 2022 Senior Flutter Developer, REKAB Technologies, Turkey Remote • Jun 2020 - Jul 2021 Flutter Developer, Ra Secret Project, Remote • Jun 2019 - May 2020 Flutter Developer, Dropp Technologies Group, Iran • Jan 2016 - Dec 2018 Android Developer, Targeting, Iran

#### **ARTICLES**

- Flutter on Embedded Devices
- Riverpod vs Bloc: Comparison of basic features
- Flutter Navigator Middleware Part 1 RouteObserver
- Flutter Navigator Middleware Part 2 Middleware Service
- Persian Articles

# **OPEN SOURCE PROJECTS - GITHUB**

- <u>Flutter Toastification</u>: Toastification is a Flutter package for displaying customizable toast messages.
- Dart Persian tools: An anthology of a variety of tools for the Persian language which you can use in all platform that dart supports
- Fantom: Open API generator for Dart & Flutter. Written with Pure Dart
- Flutter Breadcrumb: Flutter Widget that can easily create Breadcrumb in Flutter.
- More Open source Projects

### **VOLUNTARY EXPERIENCE**



Persian Flutter, Jul 2021 - Present **Community Staff** 

# **WORK EXPERIENCE IN DETAIL**



#### Senior Flutter Developer Remote, Germany | Sep 2022 - Present

Snapp Mobile is part of the Snapp companies, a stable parent company with a long history of successful project deliveries and access to nearly 150 designers and developers for project scalability and expertise.

- Struct Clean Architecture based on **Riverpod** and **Freezed** in flutter.
- Worked on multiplatform app and developed the responsive component and widgets.
- Created multiple **pipelines** in **azure DevOps** system.
- Collaborated to the project that was using an agile approach



# Senior Flutter Developer Remote, Turkey | Jul 2021 - Sep 2022

Rekab City is a multi-module trip planner platform. You can easily plan your trip with public transport and get live updates about network interruptions.

- Contribute to an <u>Open API generator package for flutter</u>.
- Worked on **multimodule** (packages without dependencies) architecture.
- Struct Architecture based on MobX and Freezed in flutter.
- Worked with **Mapbox** as the main map of the app.
- Used Hive as main local database.
- Created a completely customized design system.
- Worked with background services.



# **Flutter Developer**

# Iran, Gorgan | Jun 2019 - May 2020

Dropp Technologies is a company Which develops Mobile and Web applications. I have worked on several applications in Dropp and learned various concepts.

- Struct an architecture base on Bloc and Equatable.
- Use **Stripe methodology** for payments.
- Construct chat part with socket.io to increase the speed in comparison with Firebase.
- Work with animations and transitions in flutter.
- Experienced Google map package and Google services.

#### **SKILLS**

• Flutter: Expert

• Android : Expert

• Java: Advanced

• Kotlin: Good

• Swift: Good

• **Python**: Good

Riverpod, Bloc, Provider ...
Teamwork

MVVM, MVP, Clean

Http, Dio, Socket

GetIt

• Isar, Hive, Sqfentity

CI/CD: Azure, Code magic,

GitHub actions

problem-solving

Active learning

· Time management